http://www.kyledesigns.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Search
.
Help
Shop Gifts & Accessories »
Compact Mirrors
Classic Engraved Gifts »
Shop All Home Accents »
Ceiling Fan Pulls
Shop All Ornaments »
Animal Ornaments
Professional Ornaments
Wholesale Craft Supply »
Night Light Bases & Bulbs
Customize Any Gift »
Create the Perfect Gift For Any Interest - Put Kyle's 500+ Designs on Any Gift - Fast & Easy!
Metal Wallets
Shop All Office Gifts »
Custom Business Gifts »
Choose-Your-Design Gifts »
Customize Your Reel
Shop Badges & Lanyards »
Bulk Key Reels
All Gifts for Her »
Bridesmaids
Gifts for Women »
All Gifts for Him »
Groomsmen
Gifts for Men »
Shop All Occasions »
Father's Day Gifts »
Birthday Gifts »
Wedding Gifts »
Retirement Gifts »
Shop By Recipient »
Shop 100 Occupations »
Veterinarian
Shop 75 Animals & Pets »
Pig
Shop 40 Sports & Games »
Swimming
Shop 50 Hobbies »
Aviation
Drama
Knitting
Train
Shop All Foods & Nature »
Iris
Shop 20 Religions »
Buddhist
Christian
Jewish
Shop 40 Symbols »
Anchor
Hand
Shop 50 Art & Music »
Art Deco
Asian
Egyptian
Monogram Letters »
Numbers »
Shop 500+ Interests »
Customer Service »
Customize Any Gift
Unique Custom Gifts »
Custom Office Items »
Manage Your Account
View Messages (10)
Your Account Details
You are signed in as:
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: * To personalize your experienceYour information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)* To improve our website(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.* To improve customer service(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)* To process transactions
(Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
* To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies? Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'Your Account Details' page.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.kyledesigns.com/terms-conditions/Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on October 7, 2019.Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.https://www.kylesdesigns.com/468 Lindbergh Ave.Livermore, CA 94551USAhttps://www.kylesdesigns.com/contact-us/925-454-5340This policy is powered by Trust Guard, your PCI compliance authority.
Back to Top
Original Designs Made in USA
Quality Gifts Since 1982
Custom Crafted Just For You
In-House Engraving
Quick Ship from California
CONTACT
800.551.5953
468 Lindbergh Ave.
© Kyle Design® 1999-2020. All Rights Reserved.
Connect With Us
Our Newsletter Sign up for occasional specials and new product announcements
Your First Name:
Your Email Address:
Creating Unique Gifts In Exclusive Designs Since 1982
